ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/176 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Western States (2), Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Women's Issues, Black and white photograph (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Images digitized from the collection., Black and white photograph (Box 28)